"","ID","word","nugget","argument","Attack"
"1",4677,"Heimdal","O","B-Organization","DiscoverVulnerability"
"2",4677,"Security","O","I-Organization","DiscoverVulnerability"
"3",4677,"also","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"4",4677,"claims","I-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"5",4677,"RIG","O","B-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"6",4677,"attempts","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"7",4677,"to","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"8",4677,"exploit","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"9",4677,"vulnerabilities","O","B-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"10",4677,"Internet","O","B-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"11",4677,"Explorer","O","I-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"12",4677,"Silverlight","O","B-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"13",4677,"Flash","O","B-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"14",4677,"Player","O","I-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"15",4677,"Microsoft","O","B-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"16",4677,"Edge","O","I-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"17",4677,"CVE-2015-8651","O","B-CVE","DiscoverVulnerability"
"18",4677,"CVE-2015-5122","O","B-CVE","DiscoverVulnerability"
"19",4677,"Flash","O","B-System","DiscoverVulnerability"
"20",4677,"CVE-2016-4117","O","B-CVE","DiscoverVulnerability"
"21",4677,"CVE-2016-1019","O","B-CVE","DiscoverVulnerability"
"22",4677,"CVE-2016-7200","O","B-CVE","DiscoverVulnerability"
"23",4677,"CVE-2016-7201","O","B-CVE","DiscoverVulnerability"
"24",4677,"Microsoft","O","B-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"25",4677,"Edge","O","I-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"26",4677,"CVE-2016-3298","O","B-CVE","DiscoverVulnerability"
"27",4677,"Internet","O","B-System","DiscoverVulnerability"
"28",4677,"Explorer","O","I-System","DiscoverVulnerability"
"29",4677,"versions","O","B-Version","DiscoverVulnerability"
"30",4677,"9","O","I-Version","DiscoverVulnerability"
"31",4677,"10","O","B-Version","DiscoverVulnerability"
"32",4677,"11","O","B-Version","DiscoverVulnerability"
"33",4677,"CVE-2016-0034","O","B-CVE","DiscoverVulnerability"
"34",5656,"infecting","O","B-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"35",5656,"the","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"36",5656,"victim","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"37",5656,"’s","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"38",5656,"installing","O","B-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"39",5656,"the","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"40",5656,"Cerber","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"41",5656,"ransomware","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"42",6608,"encrypt","O","B-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"43",6608,"user","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"44",6608,"’s","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"45",6608,"demand","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"46",6608,"a","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"47",6608,"ransom","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"48",11613,"vulnerabilities","O","B-Vulnerability","Ransom"
"49",11613,"already","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"50",11613,"patched","I-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"51",11613,"the","O","B-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"52",11613,"software","O","I-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"53",11613,"developer","O","I-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"54",881,"Sucuri","O","B-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"55",881,"detected","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"56",881,"the","O","B-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"57",881,"vulnerability","O","I-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"58",881,"became","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"59",881,"public","I-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"60",881,"last","O","B-Time","DiscoverVulnerability"
"61",881,"Monday","O","I-Time","DiscoverVulnerability"
"62",1880,"a","O","B-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"63",1880,"vulnerability","O","I-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"64",1880,"the","O","B-System","DiscoverVulnerability"
"65",1880,"WordPress","O","I-System","DiscoverVulnerability"
"66",1880,"REST","O","I-System","DiscoverVulnerability"
"67",1880,"API","O","I-System","DiscoverVulnerability"
"68",1880,"the","O","B-Person","DiscoverVulnerability"
"69",1880,"WordPress","O","I-Person","DiscoverVulnerability"
"70",1880,"team","O","I-Person","DiscoverVulnerability"
"71",1880,"fixed","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"72",1880,"almost","O","B-Time","PatchVulnerability"
"73",1880,"two","O","I-Time","PatchVulnerability"
"74",1880,"weeks","O","I-Time","PatchVulnerability"
"75",1880,"ago","O","I-Time","PatchVulnerability"
"76",1880,"they","O","B-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"77",1880,"published","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"78",1880,"public","I-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"79",1880,"details","I-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"80",1880,"last","O","B-Time","DiscoverVulnerability"
"81",1880,"Monday","O","I-Time","DiscoverVulnerability"
"82",569,"InterContinental","O","B-Organization","DiscoverVulnerability"
"83",569,"Hotels","O","I-Organization","DiscoverVulnerability"
"84",569,"Group","O","I-Organization","DiscoverVulnerability"
"85",569,"late","O","B-Time","DiscoverVulnerability"
"86",569,"last","O","I-Time","DiscoverVulnerability"
"87",569,"week","O","I-Time","DiscoverVulnerability"
"88",569,"payment","O","B-System","DiscoverVulnerability"
"89",569,"card","O","I-System","DiscoverVulnerability"
"90",569,"systems","O","I-System","DiscoverVulnerability"
"91",569,"1,000","O","B-Number","DiscoverVulnerability"
"92",569,"its","O","B-Organization","DiscoverVulnerability"
"93",569,"hotels","O","I-Organization","DiscoverVulnerability"
"94",569,"had","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"95",569,"been","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"96",569,"breached","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"97",2567,"The","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"98",2567,"company","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"99",2567,"February","O","B-Time","Databreach"
"100",2567,"a","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"101",2567,"credit","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"102",2567,"card","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"103",2567,"breach","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"104",2567,"12","O","B-Number","Databreach"
"105",2567,"its","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"106",2567,"hotels","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"107",2567,"restaurants","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"108",3564,"second","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"109",3564,"breach","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"110",3564,"hotels","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"111",3564,"between","O","B-Time","Databreach"
"112",3564,"Sept.","O","I-Time","Databreach"
"113",3564,"29","O","I-Time","Databreach"
"114",3564,"and","O","I-Time","Databreach"
"115",3564,"Dec.","O","I-Time","Databreach"
"116",3564,"29","O","I-Time","Databreach"
"117",4555,"payment","O","B-PII","Databreach"
"118",4555,"card","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"119",4555,"data","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"120",4555,"was","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"121",4555,"accessed","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"122",5534,"the","O","B-Malware","Databreach"
"123",5534,"variant","O","I-Malware","Databreach"
"124",5534,"system","O","B-System","Databreach"
"125",5534,"siphoned","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"126",5534,"track","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"127",5534,"data","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"128",5534,"customers","O","B-Person","Databreach"
"129",5534,"card","O","B-PII","Databreach"
"130",5534,"number","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"131",5534,"expiration","O","B-Data","Databreach"
"132",5534,"date","O","I-Data","Databreach"
"133",5534,"internal","O","B-Data","Databreach"
"134",5534,"verification","O","I-Data","Databreach"
"135",5534,"code","O","I-Data","Databreach"
"136",6489,"the","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"137",6489,"first","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"138",6489,"breach","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"139",6489,"malware","O","B-Malware","Databreach"
"140",6489,"servers","O","B-System","Databreach"
"141",6489,"credit","O","B-PII","Databreach"
"142",6489,"cards","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"143",6489,"from","O","B-Time","Databreach"
"144",6489,"August","O","I-Time","Databreach"
"145",6489,"to","O","I-Time","Databreach"
"146",6489,"December","O","I-Time","Databreach"
"147",6489,"2016","O","I-Time","Databreach"
"148",7420,"That","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"149",7420,"breach","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"150",7420,"hotels","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"151",7420,"bars","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"152",7420,"restaurants","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"153",7420,"hotels","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"154",7420,"Michael","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"155",7420,"Jordan","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"156",7420,"’s","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"157",7420,"Steak","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"158",7420,"House","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"159",7420,"and","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"160",7420,"InterContinental","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"161",7420,"Chicago","O","B-GPE","Databreach"
"162",7420,"Copper","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"163",7420,"Lounge","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"164",7420,"Intercontinental","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"165",7420,"Los","O","B-GPE","Databreach"
"166",7420,"Angeles","O","I-GPE","Databreach"
"167",8328,"properties","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"168",8328,"the","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"169",8328,"second","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"170",8328,"breach","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"171",12159,"this","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"172",12159,"most","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"173",12159,"recent","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"174",12159,"breach","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"175",12159,"U.S.-based","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"176",12159,"chains","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"177",14650,"a","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"178",14650,"breach","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"179",14650,"late","O","B-Time","Databreach"
"180",14650,"August","O","I-Time","Databreach"
"181",14650,"cards","O","B-PII","Databreach"
"182",14650,"from","O","B-Time","Databreach"
"183",14650,"Feb.","O","I-Time","Databreach"
"184",14650,"16","O","I-Time","Databreach"
"185",14650,",","O","I-Time","Databreach"
"186",14650,"2016","O","I-Time","Databreach"
"187",14650,"and","O","I-Time","Databreach"
"188",14650,"July","O","I-Time","Databreach"
"189",14650,"its","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"190",14650,"restaurants","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"191",14650,"hotels","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"192",46,"Splunk","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"193",46,"addressed","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"194",46,"vulnerabilities","O","B-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"195",46,"Enterprise","O","B-Software","PatchVulnerability"
"196",46,"Light","O","B-Software","PatchVulnerability"
"197",46,"products","O","I-Software","PatchVulnerability"
"198",3043,"issues","O","B-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"199",3043,"Splunk","O","B-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"200",3043,"upgrading","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"201",3043,"latest","O","B-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"202",3043,"release","O","I-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"203",3043,"applying","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"204",4036,"Splunk","O","B-Software","PatchVulnerability"
"205",4036,"Enterprise","O","I-Software","PatchVulnerability"
"206",4036,"Splunk","O","B-Software","PatchVulnerability"
"207",4036,"Light","O","I-Software","PatchVulnerability"
"208",4036,"releases","O","B-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"209",4036,"future","O","B-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"210",4036,"releases","O","I-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"211",4036,"fixes","O","B-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"212",4036,"vulnerabilities","O","B-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"213",4036,"bug","O","B-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"214",4036,"fixes","O","I-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"215",4036,"advisory","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"216",4036,"published","I-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"217",4036,"Splunk","O","B-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"218",5018,"severe","O","B-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"219",5018,"issue","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"220",5018,"fixed","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"221",5018,"the","O","B-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"222",5018,"company","O","I-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"223",5018,"cross-site","O","B-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"224",5018,"scripting","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"225",5018,"(","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"226",5018,"XSS","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"227",5018,"the","O","B-System","PatchVulnerability"
"228",5018,"Web","O","I-System","PatchVulnerability"
"229",5018,"interface","O","I-System","PatchVulnerability"
"230",5018,"tracked","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"231",5018,"as","I-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"232",5018,"CVE-2018-7427","O","B-CVE","DiscoverVulnerability"
"233",5984,"severe","O","B-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"234",5984,"vulnerability","O","I-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"235",5984,"DoS","O","B-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"236",5984,"flaw","O","I-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"237",5984,"tracked","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"238",5984,"as","I-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"239",5984,"CVE-2018-7432","O","B-CVE","DiscoverVulnerability"
"240",5984,"be","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"241",5984,"exploited","I-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"242",5984,"using","O","B-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"243",5984,"malicious","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"244",5984,"HTTP","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"245",5984,"requests","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"246",5984,"sent","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"247",5984,"to","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"248",5984,"Splunkd","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"249",6924,"issue","O","B-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"250",6924,"tracked","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"251",6924,"as","I-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"252",6924,"company","O","B-Organization","DiscoverVulnerability"
"253",7844,"company","O","B-Organization","DiscoverVulnerability"
"254",7844,"addressed","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"255",7844,"denial-of-service","O","B-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"256",7844,"(","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"257",7844,"DoS","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"258",7844,"tracked","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"259",7844,"as","I-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"260",7844,"CVE-2018-7429","O","B-CVE","DiscoverVulnerability"
"261",7844,"be","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"262",7844,"exploited","I-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"263",7844,"sending","O","B-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"264",7844,"a","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"265",7844,"specially","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"266",7844,"crafted","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"267",7844,"HTTP","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"268",7844,"request","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"269",7844,"to","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"270",7844,"Splunkd","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"271",8731,"flaw","O","B-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"272",8731,"addressed","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"273",8731,"vendor","O","B-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"274",8731,"tracked","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"275",8731,"as","I-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"276",8731,"CVE-2018-7431","O","B-CVE","DiscoverVulnerability"
"277",8731,"issue","O","B-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"278",8731,"allows","O","B-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"279",8731,"an","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"280",8731,"authenticated","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"281",8731,"attacker","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"282",8731,"to","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"283",8731,"download","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"284",8731,"arbitrary","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"285",8731,"files","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"286",8731,"Django","O","B-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"287",8731,"app","O","I-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"288",9583,"vulnerability","O","B-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"289",9583,"been","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"290",9583,"rated","I-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"291",10387,"vendor","O","B-Organization","DiscoverVulnerability"
"292",10387,"found","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"293",10387,"vulnerabilities","O","B-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"294",10387,"been","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"295",10387,"exploited","I-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"296",58,"The","O","B-Person","DiscoverVulnerability"
"297",58,"boss","O","I-Person","DiscoverVulnerability"
"298",58,"a","O","B-Organization","DiscoverVulnerability"
"299",58,"company","O","I-Organization","DiscoverVulnerability"
"300",58,"held","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"301",58,"to","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"302",58,"ransom","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"303",58,"computer","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"304",58,"hackers","O","I-Person","Ransom"
"305",1057,"Kettell","O","B-Organization","Ransom"
"306",1057,"Video","O","I-Organization","Ransom"
"307",1057,"Productions","O","I-Organization","Ransom"
"308",1057,"hackers","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"309",1057,"encrypted","O","B-Capabilities","Ransom"
"310",1057,"all","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"311",1057,"his","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"312",1057,"files","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"313",1057,"demanded","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"314",1057,"money","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"315",4048,"They","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"316",4048,"staff","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"317",4048,"demanded","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"318",4048,"£","O","B-Money","Ransom"
"319",4048,"online","O","B-PaymentMethod","Ransom"
"320",4048,"currency","O","I-PaymentMethod","Ransom"
"321",4048,"bitcoins","O","I-PaymentMethod","Ransom"
"322",3617,"Netflix","O","B-Organization","Ransom"
"323",3617,"the","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"324",3617,"leaked","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"325",3617,"episodes","O","B-Data","Databreach"
"326",9248,"Their","O","B-Data","Databreach"
"327",9248,"files","O","I-Data","Databreach"
"328",9248,"were","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"329",9248,"stolen","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"330",10077,"Ransomware","O","B-Capabilities","Databreach"
"331",10077,"encrypts","O","I-Capabilities","Databreach"
"332",10077,"the","O","I-Capabilities","Databreach"
"333",10077,"files","O","I-Capabilities","Databreach"
"334",10077,"on","O","I-Capabilities","Databreach"
"335",10077,"a","O","I-Capabilities","Databreach"
"336",10077,"computer","O","I-Capabilities","Databreach"
"337",10849,"Victims","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"338",10849,"pay","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"339",10849,"a","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"340",10849,"fee","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"341",10849,"(","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"342",12193,"Late","O","B-Time","Ransom"
"343",12193,"last","O","I-Time","Ransom"
"344",12193,"year","O","I-Time","Ransom"
"345",12193,"TheDarkOverlord","O","B-Organization","Ransom"
"346",12193,"hacked","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"347",12193,"Larson","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"348",12193,"Studios","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"349",12193,"downloaded","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"350",12193,"files","O","B-Data","Databreach"
"351",13686,"Larson","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"352",13686,"Studios","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"353",13686,"the","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"354",13686,"extortion","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"355",13686,"demands","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"356",14063,"Netflix","O","B-Organization","Ransom"
"357",14063,"pay","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"358",15416,"their","O","B-Data","Ransom"
"359",15416,"popular","O","I-Data","Ransom"
"360",15416,"series","O","I-Data","Ransom"
"361",15416,"leaked","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"362",15627,"Netflix","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"363",15627,"Larson","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"364",15627,"Studios","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"365",15627,"are","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"366",15627,"(","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"367",15627,"were","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"368",15627,")","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"369",15627,"they","O","B-Organization","Ransom"
"370",15627,"were","O","B-Capabilities","Ransom"
"371",15627,"not","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"372",15627,"infected","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"373",15627,"with","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"374",15627,"Ransomware","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"375",15627,"have","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"376",15627,"complete","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"377",15627,"access","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"378",15627,"their","O","B-Data","Databreach"
"379",15627,"files","O","I-Data","Databreach"
"380",73,"A","O","B-Person","Databreach"
"381",73,"local","O","I-Person","Databreach"
"382",73,"resident","O","I-Person","Databreach"
"383",73,"receiving","B-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"384",73,"an","O","B-File","Phishing"
"385",73,"email","O","I-File","Phishing"
"386",73,"claiming","B-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"387",73,"to","I-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"388",73,"be","I-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"389",73,"HMRC","O","B-Organization","Phishing"
"390",73,"receive","O","B-Purpose","Phishing"
"391",73,"a","O","I-Purpose","Phishing"
"392",73,"tax","O","I-Purpose","Phishing"
"393",73,"refund","O","I-Purpose","Phishing"
"394",73,"£","O","B-Money","Phishing"
"395",1072,"the","O","B-File","Phishing"
"396",1072,"fake","O","I-File","Phishing"
"397",1072,"HMRC","O","I-File","Phishing"
"398",1072,"email","O","I-File","Phishing"
"399",1072,"advises","B-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"400",1072,"you","O","B-Person","Phishing"
"401",1072,"click","O","B-Capabilities","Phishing"
"402",1072,"on","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"403",1072,"a","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"404",1072,"link","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"405",1072,"to","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"406",1072,"complete","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"407",1072,"and","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"408",1072,"submit","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"409",1072,"the","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"410",1072,"refund","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"411",1072,"form","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"412",2071,"take","O","B-Capabilities","Phishing"
"413",2071,"you","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"414",2071,"to","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"415",2071,"a","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"416",2071,"fraudulent","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"417",2071,"website","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"418",2071,"supply","O","B-Purpose","Phishing"
"419",2071,"your","O","I-Purpose","Phishing"
"420",2071,"name","O","I-Purpose","Phishing"
"421",2071,",","O","I-Purpose","Phishing"
"422",2071,"address","O","I-Purpose","Phishing"
"423",2071,",","O","I-Purpose","Phishing"
"424",2071,"and","O","I-Purpose","Phishing"
"425",3070,"The","O","B-Website","Phishing"
"426",3070,"fake","O","I-Website","Phishing"
"427",3070,"HMRC","O","I-Website","Phishing"
"428",3070,"site","O","I-Website","Phishing"
"429",3070,"supply","O","B-Purpose","Phishing"
"430",3070,"your","O","I-Purpose","Phishing"
"431",3070,"credit","O","I-Purpose","Phishing"
"432",3070,"card","O","I-Purpose","Phishing"
"433",3070,"numbers","O","I-Purpose","Phishing"
"434",5044,"the","O","B-Data","Phishing"
"435",5044,"information","O","I-Data","Phishing"
"436",5044,"will","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"437",5044,"be","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"438",5044,"collected","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"439",5044,"scammers","O","B-Person","Databreach"
"440",5044,"commit","O","B-Purpose","Databreach"
"441",5044,"fraud","O","I-Purpose","Databreach"
"442",5044,"steal","O","B-Purpose","Databreach"
"443",5044,"your","O","I-Purpose","Databreach"
"444",5044,"identity","O","I-Purpose","Databreach"
"445",6010,"you","O","B-Person","Databreach"
"446",6010,"have","B-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"447",6010,"received","I-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"448",6010,"an","O","B-Organization","Phishing"
"449",6010,"HMRC","O","I-Organization","Phishing"
"450",6010,"phishing/bogus","O","B-File","Phishing"
"451",6010,"email","O","I-File","Phishing"
"452",291,"Mozilla","O","B-Organization","Phishing"
"453",291,"has","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"454",291,"recently","I-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"455",291,"fixed","I-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"456",291,"multiple","O","B-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"457",291,"security","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"458",291,"flaws","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"459",291,"Thunderbird","O","B-Software","PatchVulnerability"
"460",291,"60.3","O","B-Version","PatchVulnerability"
"461",1290,"These","O","B-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"462",1290,"vulnerabilities","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"463",1290,"a","O","B-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"464",1290,"critical","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"465",1290,"security","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"466",1290,"bug","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"467",1290,"affected","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"468",1290,"Mozilla","O","B-Organization","DiscoverVulnerability"
"469",1290,"Firefox","O","B-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"470",1290,"Firefox","O","B-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"471",1290,"ESR","O","I-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"472",1290,"browsers","O","I-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"473",2289,"Last","O","B-Time","DiscoverVulnerability"
"474",2289,"week","O","I-Time","DiscoverVulnerability"
"475",2289,"Mozilla","O","B-Organization","DiscoverVulnerability"
"476",2289,"patched","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"477",2289,"multiple","O","B-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"478",2289,"security","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"479",2289,"flaws","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"480",2289,"Thunderbird","O","B-Software","PatchVulnerability"
"481",2289,"60.3","O","B-Version","PatchVulnerability"
"482",2289,"a","O","B-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"483",2289,"critical","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"484",2289,"security","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"485",2289,"flaw","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"486",3288,"community","O","B-Person","PatchVulnerability"
"487",3288,"members","O","I-Person","PatchVulnerability"
"488",3288,"and","O","I-Person","PatchVulnerability"
"489",3288,"developers","O","I-Person","PatchVulnerability"
"490",3288,"Mozilla","O","B-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"491",3288,"discovered","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"492",3288,"reported","O","B-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"493",3288,"memory","O","I-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"494",3288,"safety","O","I-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"495",3288,"bugs","O","I-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"496",3288,"affected","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"497",3288,"Thunderbird","O","B-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"498",3288,"email","O","I-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"499",3288,"client","O","I-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"500",3288,"had","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"501",3288,"impacted","I-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"502",3288,"Firefox","O","B-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"503",3288,"Firefox","O","B-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"504",3288,"ESR","O","I-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"505",4281,"bugs","O","B-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"506",4281,"memory","O","B-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"507",4281,"corruption","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"508",4281,"be","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"509",4281,"exploited","I-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"510",4281,"run","O","B-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"511",4281,"arbitrary","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"512",4281,"code","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"513",5262,"Mozilla","O","B-Organization","DiscoverVulnerability"
"514",5262,"has","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"515",5262,"fixed","I-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"516",5262,"the","O","B-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"517",5262,"bugs","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"518",5262,"Firefox","O","B-Software","PatchVulnerability"
"519",5262,"63","O","B-Version","PatchVulnerability"
"520",5262,"Firefox","O","B-Software","PatchVulnerability"
"521",5262,"ESR","O","I-Software","PatchVulnerability"
"522",5262,"60.3","O","B-Version","PatchVulnerability"
"523",5262,"Thunderbird","O","B-Software","PatchVulnerability"
"524",5262,"60.3","O","B-Version","PatchVulnerability"
"525",6227,"Mozilla","O","B-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"526",6227,"released","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"527",6227,"fixes","O","B-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"528",6227,"vulnerabilities","O","B-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"529",6227,"affecting","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"530",6227,"Thunderbird","O","B-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"531",12567,"flaws","O","B-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"532",12567,"be","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"533",12567,"exploited","I-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"534",12567,"Thunderbird","O","B-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"535",12567,"browser","O","B-System","DiscoverVulnerability"
"536",13083,"Mozilla","O","B-Organization","DiscoverVulnerability"
"537",13083,"patched","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"538",13083,"multiple","O","B-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"539",13083,"vulnerabilities","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"540",13083,"Thunderbird","O","B-Software","PatchVulnerability"
"541",13083,"Firefox","O","B-Software","PatchVulnerability"
"542",13083,"last","O","B-Time","PatchVulnerability"
"543",13083,"month","O","I-Time","PatchVulnerability"
"544",13538,"Mozilla","O","B-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"545",13538,"released","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"546",13538,"a","O","B-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"547",13538,"fix","O","I-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"548",13538,"critical","O","B-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"549",13538,"code","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"550",13538,"execution","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"551",13538,"vulnerability","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"552",13538,"affecting","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"553",13538,"Thunderbird","O","B-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"554",13538,"60.2","O","B-Version","DiscoverVulnerability"
"555",13538,"Firefox","O","B-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"556",13538,"61","O","B-Version","DiscoverVulnerability"
"557",13538,"Firefox","O","B-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"558",13538,"ESR","O","I-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"559",13538,"60.1","O","B-Version","DiscoverVulnerability"
"560",264,"Google","O","B-Organization","DiscoverVulnerability"
"561",264,"has","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"562",264,"released","I-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"563",264,"Android","O","B-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"564",264,"security","O","I-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"565",264,"update","O","I-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"566",264,"the","O","B-Device","PatchVulnerability"
"567",264,"supported","O","I-Device","PatchVulnerability"
"568",264,"Nexus","O","I-Device","PatchVulnerability"
"569",264,"Pixel","O","B-Device","PatchVulnerability"
"570",264,"devices","O","I-Device","PatchVulnerability"
"571",1263,"Android","O","B-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"572",1263,"security","O","I-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"573",1263,"update","O","I-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"574",1263,"fixes","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"575",1263,"59","O","B-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"576",1263,"issues","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"577",1263,"the","O","B-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"578",1263,"first","O","I-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"579",1263,"update","O","I-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"580",1263,"devices","O","B-Device","PatchVulnerability"
"581",1263,"Android","O","B-System","PatchVulnerability"
"582",1263,"9.0","O","B-Version","PatchVulnerability"
"583",1263,"Pie","O","I-Version","PatchVulnerability"
"584",1263,"the","O","B-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"585",1263,"search","O","I-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"586",1263,"giant","O","I-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"587",1263,"released","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"588",1263,"its","O","B-Version","PatchVulnerability"
"589",1263,"latest","O","I-Version","PatchVulnerability"
"590",1263,"Android","O","I-Version","PatchVulnerability"
"591",1263,"version","O","I-Version","PatchVulnerability"
"592",1263,"last","O","B-Time","PatchVulnerability"
"593",1263,"month","O","I-Time","PatchVulnerability"
"594",2262,"It","O","B-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"595",2262,"addresses","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"596",2262,"vulnerabilities","O","B-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"597",3261,"Google","O","B-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"598",3261,"being","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"599",3261,"affected","I-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"600",3261,"the","O","B-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"601",3261,"security","O","I-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"602",3261,"issues","O","I-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"603",3261,"have","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"604",3261,"been","I-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"605",3261,"fixed","I-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"606",3261,"the","O","B-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"607",3261,"new","O","I-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"608",3261,"update","O","I-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"609",5235,"Essential","O","B-Device","PatchVulnerability"
"610",5235,"Products","O","I-Device","PatchVulnerability"
"611",5235,"has","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"612",5235,"also","I-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"613",5235,"separately","I-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"614",5235,"released","I-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"615",5235,"Android","O","B-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"616",5235,"security","O","I-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"617",5235,"update","O","I-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"618",5235,"the","O","B-Device","PatchVulnerability"
"619",5235,"Essential","O","I-Device","PatchVulnerability"
"620",5235,"Phone","O","I-Device","PatchVulnerability"
"621",6200,"Google","O","B-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"622",6200,"Android","O","B-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"623",6200,"security","O","I-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"624",6200,"patch","O","I-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"625",6200,"2018-09-01","O","B-Time","PatchVulnerability"
"626",6200,"addresses","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"627",6200,"24","O","B-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"628",6200,"issues","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"629",6200,"the","O","B-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"630",6200,"security","O","I-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"631",6200,"patch","O","I-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"632",6200,"2018-09-05","O","B-Time","PatchVulnerability"
"633",6200,"fixes","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"634",6200,"35","O","B-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"635",6200,"issues","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"636",7140,"The","O","B-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"637",7140,"update","O","I-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"638",7140,"fixes","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"639",7140,"vulnerabilities","O","B-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"640",7140,"let","O","B-Capabilities","PatchVulnerability"
"641",7140,"a","O","I-Capabilities","PatchVulnerability"
"642",7140,"remote","O","I-Capabilities","PatchVulnerability"
"643",7140,"attacker","O","I-Capabilities","PatchVulnerability"
"644",7140,"execute","O","I-Capabilities","PatchVulnerability"
"645",7140,"arbitrary","O","I-Capabilities","PatchVulnerability"
"646",7140,"code","O","I-Capabilities","PatchVulnerability"
"647",7140,"using","O","I-Capabilities","PatchVulnerability"
"648",7140,"a","O","I-Capabilities","PatchVulnerability"
"649",7140,"specially","O","I-Capabilities","PatchVulnerability"
"650",7140,"crafted","O","I-Capabilities","PatchVulnerability"
"651",7140,"file","O","I-Capabilities","PatchVulnerability"
"652",8057,"it","O","B-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"653",8057,"fixes","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"654",8057,"issues","O","B-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"655",8057,"the","O","B-Software","PatchVulnerability"
"656",8057,"Android","O","I-Software","PatchVulnerability"
"657",8057,"runtime","O","I-Software","PatchVulnerability"
"658",8057,"framework","O","B-Software","PatchVulnerability"
"659",8057,"library","O","B-Software","PatchVulnerability"
"660",10572,"The","O","B-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"661",10572,"update","O","I-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"662",10572,"improves","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"663",10572,"all","O","B-Device","PatchVulnerability"
"664",10572,"Pixel","O","I-Device","PatchVulnerability"
"665",10572,"devices","O","I-Device","PatchVulnerability"
"666",278,"D-Link","O","B-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"667",278,"warnings","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"668",278,"security","O","B-Person","DiscoverVulnerability"
"669",278,"researchers","O","I-Person","DiscoverVulnerability"
"670",278,"company","O","B-Organization","DiscoverVulnerability"
"671",278,"routers","O","B-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"672",1277,"Silesian","O","B-Person","DiscoverVulnerability"
"673",1277,"University","O","I-Person","DiscoverVulnerability"
"674",1277,"of","O","I-Person","DiscoverVulnerability"
"675",1277,"Technology","O","I-Person","DiscoverVulnerability"
"676",1277,"researcher","O","I-Person","DiscoverVulnerability"
"677",1277,"Błazej","O","I-Person","DiscoverVulnerability"
"678",1277,"Adamczyk","O","I-Person","DiscoverVulnerability"
"679",1277,"contacted","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"680",1277,"D-Link","O","B-Organization","DiscoverVulnerability"
"681",1277,"last","O","B-Time","DiscoverVulnerability"
"682",1277,"May","O","I-Time","DiscoverVulnerability"
"683",1277,"three","O","B-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"684",1277,"vulnerabilities","O","I-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"685",1277,"affecting","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"686",1277,"router","O","B-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"687",1277,"models","O","I-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"688",2276,"the","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"689",2276,"warning","I-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"690",2276,"D-Link","O","B-Organization","DiscoverVulnerability"
"691",2276,"patched","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"692",2276,"routers","O","B-Device","PatchVulnerability"
"693",2276,"reveal","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"694",2276,"models","O","B-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"695",3275,"prompting","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"696",3275,"Adamczyk","O","B-Person","DiscoverVulnerability"
"697",3275,"D-Link","O","B-Organization","DiscoverVulnerability"
"698",3275,"revealed","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"699",3275,"routers","O","B-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"700",3275,"would","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"701",3275,"not","I-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"702",3275,"get","I-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"703",3275,"a","O","B-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"704",3275,"security","O","I-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"705",3275,"patch","O","I-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"706",4268,"The","O","B-Device","PatchVulnerability"
"707",4268,"D-Link","O","I-Device","PatchVulnerability"
"708",4268,"models","O","I-Device","PatchVulnerability"
"709",4268,"affected","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"710",4268,"the","O","B-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"711",4268,"DWR-116","O","I-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"712",4268,"DWR-140L","O","B-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"713",4268,"DWR-512","O","B-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"714",4268,"DWR-640L","O","B-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"715",4268,"DWR-712","O","B-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"716",4268,"DWR-912","O","B-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"717",4268,"DWR-921","O","B-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"718",4268,"DWR-111","O","B-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"719",4268,"2013","O","B-Time","DiscoverVulnerability"
"720",4268,"the","O","B-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"721",4268,"DIR-640L","O","I-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"722",4268,"first","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"723",4268,"appearing","I-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"724",4268,"2012","O","B-Time","DiscoverVulnerability"
"725",4268,"the","O","B-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"726",4268,"DWR-111","O","I-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"727",4268,"2014","O","B-Time","DiscoverVulnerability"
"728",6214,"Adamczyk","O","B-Person","DiscoverVulnerability"
"729",6214,"released","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"730",6214,"details","I-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"731",6214,"the","O","B-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"732",6214,"security","O","I-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"733",6214,"flaws","O","I-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"734",6214,"D-Link","O","B-Organization","DiscoverVulnerability"
"735",6214,"address","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"736",6214,"the","O","B-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"737",6214,"issues","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"738",7154,"D-Link","O","B-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"739",7154,"has","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"740",7154,"failed","I-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"741",7154,"to","I-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"742",7154,"address","I-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"743",7154,"security","O","B-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"744",7154,"vulnerabilities","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"745",7154,"affecting","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"746",7154,"its","O","B-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"747",7154,"products","O","I-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"748",7154,"being","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"749",7154,"notified","I-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"750",7154,"researchers","O","B-Person","DiscoverVulnerability"
"751",8070,"The","O","B-Person","DiscoverVulnerability"
"752",8070,"security","O","I-Person","DiscoverVulnerability"
"753",8070,"researcher","O","I-Person","DiscoverVulnerability"
"754",8070,"noted","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"755",8070,"the","O","B-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"756",8070,"new","O","I-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"757",8070,"flaw","O","I-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"758",8070,"arose","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"759",8070,"D-Link","O","B-Organization","DiscoverVulnerability"
"760",8070,"it","O","B-Organization","DiscoverVulnerability"
"761",8070,"had","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"762",8070,"fixed","I-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"763",8070,"a","O","B-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"764",8070,"prior","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"765",8070,"security","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"766",8070,"flaw","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"767",9794,"the","O","B-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"768",9794,"manufacturer","O","I-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"769",9794,"routers","O","B-Device","PatchVulnerability"
"770",9794,"unpatched","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"771",10584,"The","O","B-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"772",10584,"American","O","I-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"773",10584,"Consumer","O","I-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"774",10584,"Institute","O","I-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"775",10584,"reported","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"776",10584,"the","O","B-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"777",10584,"186","O","I-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"778",10584,"routers","O","I-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"779",10584,"contained","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"780",10584,"firmware","O","B-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"781",10584,"vulnerabilities","O","I-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"782",11313,"ACI","O","B-Organization","DiscoverVulnerability"
"783",11313,"discovered","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"784",11313,"vulnerabilities","O","B-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"785",11975,"routers","O","B-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"786",11975,"contained","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"787",11975,"12","O","B-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"788",11975,"critical","O","I-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"789",11975,"vulnerabilities","O","I-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"790",11975,"36","O","B-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"791",11975,"high-risk","O","I-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"792",11975,"vulnerabilities","O","I-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"793",13532,"get","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"794",13532,"patches","O","B-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"795",13532,"a","O","B-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"796",13532,"security","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"797",13532,"vulnerability","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"798",638,"A","B-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"799",638,"massive","I-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"800",638,"phishing","I-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"801",638,"campaign","I-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"802",638,"Google","O","B-PII","Phishing"
"803",638,"accounts","O","I-PII","Phishing"
"804",638,"Wednesday","O","B-Time","Phishing"
"805",638,"afternoon","O","I-Time","Phishing"
"806",1637,"they","O","B-Person","Phishing"
"807",1637,"received","B-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"808",1637,"emails","O","B-File","Phishing"
"809",1637,"looked","B-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"810",1637,"like","I-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"811",1637,"a","O","B-Website","Phishing"
"812",1637,"link","O","I-Website","Phishing"
"813",1637,"a","O","B-Software","Phishing"
"814",1637,"Google","O","I-Software","Phishing"
"815",1637,"Doc","O","I-Software","Phishing"
"816",1637,"appeared","B-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"817",1637,"to","I-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"818",1637,"come","I-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"819",1637,"from","I-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"820",1637,"someone","O","B-Person","Phishing"
"821",1637,"they","O","I-Person","Phishing"
"822",1637,"know","O","I-Person","Phishing"
"823",2636,"malicious","O","B-File","Phishing"
"824",2636,"emails","O","I-File","Phishing"
"825",2636,"hijack","O","B-Purpose","Phishing"
"826",2636,"their","O","I-Purpose","Phishing"
"827",2636,"accounts","O","I-Purpose","Phishing"
"828",10090,"We","O","B-Organization","Phishing"
"829",10090,"the","O","B-Website","Phishing"
"830",10090,"fake","O","I-Website","Phishing"
"831",10090,"pages","O","I-Website","Phishing"
"832",10090,"pushed","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"833",10090,"updates","O","B-Patch","PatchVulnerability"
"834",10090,"Safe","O","B-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"835",10090,"Browsing","O","I-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"836",10090,"spoofing","B-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"837",11568,"the","B-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"838",11568,"phishing","I-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"839",11568,"campaign","I-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"840",11568,"Gmail","O","B-Person","Phishing"
"841",11568,"users","O","I-Person","Phishing"
"842",912,"The","O","B-Person","Phishing"
"843",912,"hackers","O","I-Person","Phishing"
"844",912,"lock","O","B-Capabilities","Phishing"
"845",912,"these","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"846",912,"computers","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"847",912,"up","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"848",912,"demand","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"849",912,"a","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"850",912,"ransom","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"851",912,"city","O","B-Organization","Ransom"
"852",4890,"The","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"853",4890,"hackers","O","I-Person","Ransom"
"854",4890,"the","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"855",4890,"owner","O","I-Person","Ransom"
"856",4890,"asking","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"857",4890,"for","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"858",4890,"a","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"859",4890,"ransom","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"860",5863,"Ransomware","O","B-Malware","Ransom"
"861",5863,"infects","O","B-Capabilities","Ransom"
"862",5863,"computers","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"863",5863,"locks","O","B-Capabilities","Ransom"
"864",5863,"or","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"865",5863,"encrypts","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"866",5863,"their","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"867",5863,"content","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"868",5863,"demanding","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"869",5863,"a","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"870",5863,"ransom","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"871",5863,"the","O","B-Device","Ransom"
"872",5863,"machines","O","I-Device","Ransom"
"873",6807,"victims","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"874",6807,"pay","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"875",6807,"the","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"876",6807,"ransom","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"877",14010,"2015","O","B-Time","Ransom"
"878",14010,"Russia","O","B-Organization","Ransom"
"879",14010,"hacking","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"880",14010,"computers","O","B-Device","Databreach"
"881",14010,"members","O","B-Person","Databreach"
"882",14010,"Germany","O","B-GPE","Databreach"
"883",14010,"lower","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"884",14010,"house","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"885",14010,"of","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"886",14010,"parliament","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"887",14010,"the","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"888",14010,"Bundestag","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"889",14010,"stealing","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"890",14010,"data","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"891",14341,"the","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"892",14341,"attack","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"893",14341,"Sofacy","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"894",14341,"the","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"895",14341,"Russian","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"896",14341,"state","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"897",15393,"organization","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"898",15393,"has","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"899",15393,"attacked","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"900",15393,"German","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"901",15393,"Parliament","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"902",15393,"stealing","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"903",15393,"the","O","B-Data","Databreach"
"904",15393,"emails","O","I-Data","Databreach"
"905",15393,"German","O","B-Person","Databreach"
"906",15393,"members","O","I-Person","Databreach"
"907",15393,"Parliament","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"908",15393,"institution","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"909",15393,"has","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"910",15393,"attacked","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"911",15393,"NATO","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"912",15393,"headquarters","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"913",16045,"Hackers","O","B-Person","Databreach"
"914",16045,"2014","O","B-Time","Databreach"
"915",16045,"attacked","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"916",16045,"the","O","B-System","Databreach"
"917",16045,"Warsaw","O","I-System","Databreach"
"918",16045,"Stock","O","I-System","Databreach"
"919",16045,"Exchange","O","I-System","Databreach"
"920",16045,"Polish","O","B-Website","Databreach"
"921",16045,"sites","O","I-Website","Databreach"
"922",16045,"stealing","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"923",16045,"data","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"924",16080,"The","O","B-Person","Databreach"
"925",16080,"group","O","I-Person","Databreach"
"926",16080,"stole","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"927",16080,"data","O","B-Data","Databreach"
"928",16080,"released","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"929",16080,"dozens","O","B-Number","Databreach"
"930",16080,"client","O","B-PII","Databreach"
"931",16080,"log-in","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"932",16080,"data","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"933",16080,"mayhem","O","B-Purpose","Databreach"
"934",16080,"for","O","I-Purpose","Databreach"
"935",16080,"the","O","I-Purpose","Databreach"
"936",16080,"exchange","O","I-Purpose","Databreach"
"937",987,"we","O","B-Person","Databreach"
"938",987,"noticed","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"939",987,"security","O","B-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"940",987,"flaw","O","I-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"941",987,"Windows","O","B-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"942",987,"10","O","I-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"943",987,"Mobile","O","I-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"944",11107,"this","O","B-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"945",11107,"issue","O","I-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"946",11107,"does","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"947",11107,"n’t","I-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"948",11107,"exist","I-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"949",11107,"Windows","O","B-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"950",11107,"10","O","I-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"951",11107,"PCs","O","I-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"952",11792,"the","O","B-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"953",11792,"issue","O","I-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"954",11792,"is","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"955",11792,"impacting","I-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"956",11792,"Windows","O","B-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"957",11792,"10","O","I-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"958",11792,"Mobile","O","I-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"959",11792,"devices","O","I-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"960",11792,"Windows","O","B-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"961",11792,"10","O","I-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"962",11792,"Mobile","O","I-Device","DiscoverVulnerability"
"963",11792,"Version","O","B-Version","DiscoverVulnerability"
"964",11792,"1511","O","I-Version","DiscoverVulnerability"
"965",11792,"1607","O","B-Version","DiscoverVulnerability"
"966",12403,"Microsoft","O","B-Organization","DiscoverVulnerability"
"967",12403,"will","B-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"968",12403,"fix","I-PatchVulnerability","O","PatchVulnerability"
"969",12403,"this","O","B-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"970",12403,"issue","O","I-Vulnerability","PatchVulnerability"
"971",12403,"Windows","O","B-Device","PatchVulnerability"
"972",12403,"10","O","I-Device","PatchVulnerability"
"973",12403,"Mobile","O","I-Device","PatchVulnerability"
"974",1949,"The","O","B-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"975",1949,"group","O","I-Organization","PatchVulnerability"
"976",1949,"was","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"977",1949,"exporting","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"978",1949,"database","O","B-Data","Databreach"
"979",1949,"'s","O","I-Data","Databreach"
"980",1949,"a","O","B-File","Databreach"
"981",1949,"ransom","O","I-File","Databreach"
"982",1949,"note","O","I-File","Databreach"
"983",1949,"asking","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"984",1949,"owners","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"985",1949,"the","O","B-System","Ransom"
"986",1949,"hacked","O","I-System","Ransom"
"987",1949,"database","O","I-System","Ransom"
"988",1949,"pay","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"989",1949,"0.2","O","B-Money","Ransom"
"990",1949,"Bitcoin","O","I-Money","Ransom"
"991",1949,"$","O","B-Money","Ransom"
"992",1949,"Bitcoin","O","B-PaymentMethod","Ransom"
"993",1949,"wallet","O","I-PaymentMethod","Ransom"
"994",2948,"Harak1r1","O","B-Organization","Ransom"
"995",2948,"hijacked","O","B-Capabilities","Ransom"
"996",2948,"MongoDB","O","B-System","Ransom"
"997",2948,"databases","O","I-System","Ransom"
"998",2948,"victims","O","B-Organization","Ransom"
"999",2948,"have","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1000",2948,"paid","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1001",2948,"the","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1002",2948,"ransom","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1003",5898,"Harak1r1","O","B-Organization","Ransom"
"1004",5898,"ransacked","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1005",5898,"200,000","O","B-Number","Databreach"
"1006",5898,"medical","O","B-Data","Databreach"
"1007",5898,"records","O","I-Data","Databreach"
"1008",9515,"second","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"1009",9515,"group","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"1010",9515,"asks","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1011",9515,"for","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1012",9515,"0.5","O","B-Money","Ransom"
"1013",9515,"Bitcoin","O","I-Money","Ransom"
"1014",9515,"$","O","B-Money","Ransom"
"1015",9515,"companies","O","B-Organization","Ransom"
"1016",9515,"paying","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1017",9515,"0wn3d","O","B-PaymentMethod","Ransom"
"1018",9515,"'s","O","I-PaymentMethod","Ransom"
"1019",9515,"Bitcoin","O","I-PaymentMethod","Ransom"
"1020",9515,"victims","O","B-Organization","Ransom"
"1021",9515,"had","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1022",9515,"paid","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1023",9515,"his","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1024",9515,"ransom","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1025",9515,"demands","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1026",11078,"This","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1027",11078,"hacker/group","O","I-Person","Ransom"
"1028",11078,"is","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1029",11078,"asking","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1030",11078,"for","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1031",11078,"0.15","O","B-Money","Ransom"
"1032",11078,"Bitcoin","O","I-Money","Ransom"
"1033",11078,"$","O","B-Money","Ransom"
"1034",11078,"using","O","B-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1035",11078,"a","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1036",11078,"lengthier","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1037",11078,"ransom","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1038",11078,"note","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1039",11078,"he","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1040",11078,"victims","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1041",11078,"leaving","O","B-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1042",11078,"their","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1043",11078,"DB","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1044",11078,"open","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1045",11078,"over","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1046",11078,"the","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1047",11078,"Internet","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1048",11767,"threat","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1049",11767,"actor","O","I-Person","Ransom"
"1050",11767,"victims","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1051",11767,"database","O","B-Organization","Ransom"
"1052",11767,"owners","O","I-Organization","Ransom"
"1053",11767,"pay","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1054",11767,"the","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1055",11767,"ransom","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1056",13397,"recent","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1057",13397,"attacks","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1058",13397,"crooks","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1059",13397,"ask","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1060",13397,"for","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1061",13397,"a","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1062",13397,"ransom","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1063",14493,"database","O","B-Organization","Ransom"
"1064",14493,"owners","O","I-Organization","Ransom"
"1065",14493,"pay","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1066",14493,"the","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1067",14493,"ransom","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1068",1920,"GoldenEye","O","B-Malware","Ransom"
"1069",1920,"the","O","B-Malware","Ransom"
"1070",1920,"ransomware","O","I-Malware","Ransom"
"1071",1920,"imitates","B-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"1072",1920,"a","O","B-File","Phishing"
"1073",1920,"job","O","I-File","Phishing"
"1074",1920,"application","O","I-File","Phishing"
"1075",1920,"German","O","B-Person","Phishing"
"1076",1920,"speakers","O","I-Person","Phishing"
"1077",1920,"Tuesday","O","B-Time","Phishing"
"1078",6815,"The","O","B-Malware","Phishing"
"1079",6815,"ransomware","O","I-Malware","Phishing"
"1080",6815,"its","O","B-Person","Phishing"
"1081",6815,"victim","O","I-Person","Phishing"
"1082",6815,"they","O","B-Person","Phishing"
"1083",6815,"a","O","B-PaymentMethod","Phishing"
"1084",6815,"Dark","O","I-PaymentMethod","Phishing"
"1085",6815,"Web","O","I-PaymentMethod","Phishing"
"1086",6815,"portal","O","I-PaymentMethod","Phishing"
"1087",6815,"pay","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1088",6815,"the","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1089",6815,"ransom","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1090",318,"unprotected","O","B-System","Ransom"
"1091",318,"MongoDB","O","I-System","Ransom"
"1092",318,"databases","O","I-System","Ransom"
"1093",318,"wiping","O","B-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1094",318,"them","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1095",318,"demanding","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1096",318,"a","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1097",318,"ransom","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1098",3315,"the","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1099",3315,"attackers","O","I-Person","Ransom"
"1100",3315,"export","O","B-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1101",3315,"the","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1102",3315,"databases","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1103",3315,",","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1104",3315,"delete","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1105",3315,"create","O","B-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1106",3315,"a","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1107",3315,"ransom","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1108",3315,"note","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1109",4308,"the","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1110",4308,"new","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1111",4308,"Mongo","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1112",4308,"Lock","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1113",4308,"campaign","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1114",4308,"the","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1115",4308,"attackers","O","I-Person","Ransom"
"1116",4308,"connect","O","B-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1117",4308,"to","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1118",4308,"an","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1119",4308,"unprotected","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1120",4308,"database","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1121",4308,"and","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1122",4308,"delete","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1123",4308,"it","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1124",6254,"a","O","B-File","Ransom"
"1125",6254,"ransom","O","I-File","Ransom"
"1126",6254,"note","O","I-File","Ransom"
"1127",6254,"the","O","B-System","Ransom"
"1128",6254,"database","O","I-System","Ransom"
"1129",6254,"has","O","B-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1130",6254,"been","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1131",6254,"encrypted","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1132",6254,"the","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1133",6254,"victims","O","I-Person","Ransom"
"1134",6254,"need","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1135",6254,"to","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1136",6254,"pay","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1137",6254,"them","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1138",6254,"a","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1139",6254,"ransom","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1140",7194,"the","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1141",7194,"Mongo","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1142",7194,"Lock","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1143",7194,"campaign","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1144",7194,"the","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1145",7194,"attackers","O","I-Person","Ransom"
"1146",7194,"a","O","B-PaymentMethod","Ransom"
"1147",7194,"bitcoin","O","I-PaymentMethod","Ransom"
"1148",7194,"address","O","I-PaymentMethod","Ransom"
"1149",7194,"the","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1150",7194,"victim","O","I-Person","Ransom"
"1151",8109,"the","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1152",8109,"attackers","O","I-Person","Ransom"
"1153",8109,"are","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1154",8109,"exporting","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1155",8109,"the","O","B-Data","Databreach"
"1156",8109,"database","O","I-Data","Databreach"
"1157",8991,"Victims","O","B-Person","Databreach"
"1158",8991,"are","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1159",8991,"paying","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1160",8991,"ransoms","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1161",8991,"bitcoin","O","B-PaymentMethod","Ransom"
"1162",8991,"addresses","O","I-PaymentMethod","Ransom"
"1163",8991,"victims","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1164",8991,"have","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1165",8991,"been","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1166",8991,"paying","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1167",8991,"the","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1168",8991,"ransoms","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1169",9831,"bitcoin","O","B-PaymentMethod","Ransom"
"1170",9831,"address","O","I-PaymentMethod","Ransom"
"1171",9831,"ransom","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1172",9831,"payments","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1173",9831,"1.8","O","B-Money","Ransom"
"1174",9831,"bitcoins","O","I-Money","Ransom"
"1175",10620,"$","O","B-Money","Ransom"
"1176",10620,"11,000","O","I-Money","Ransom"
"1177",8543,"The","O","B-File","Ransom"
"1178",8543,"messages","O","I-File","Ransom"
"1179",8543,"impersonate","B-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"1180",8543,"law","O","B-Organization","Phishing"
"1181",8543,"enforcement","O","I-Organization","Phishing"
"1182",8543,"authority","O","I-Organization","Phishing"
"1183",8543,"ask","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1184",8543,"victims","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1185",8543,"pay","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1186",10994,"$","O","B-Money","Ransom"
"1187",10994,"paying","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1188",10994,"click","O","B-PaymentMethod","Ransom"
"1189",10994,"on","O","I-PaymentMethod","Ransom"
"1190",10994,"the","O","I-PaymentMethod","Ransom"
"1191",10994,"payment","O","I-PaymentMethod","Ransom"
"1192",10994,"section","O","I-PaymentMethod","Ransom"
"1193",4922,"An","B-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"1194",4922,"attack","I-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"1195",4922,"a","O","B-Organization","Phishing"
"1196",4922,"business","O","I-Organization","Phishing"
"1197",4922,"receives","B-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"1198",4922,"an","O","B-File","Phishing"
"1199",4922,"email","O","I-File","Phishing"
"1200",4922,"appears","B-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"1201",4922,"HSBC","O","B-Organization","Phishing"
"1202",4922,"the","O","B-Organization","Phishing"
"1203",4922,"largest","O","I-Organization","Phishing"
"1204",4922,"banking","O","I-Organization","Phishing"
"1205",4922,"finance","O","B-Organization","Phishing"
"1206",4922,"organizations","O","I-Organization","Phishing"
"1207",9511,"The","O","B-Malware","Phishing"
"1208",9511,"malware","O","I-Malware","Phishing"
"1209",9511,"the","O","B-Person","Phishing"
"1210",9511,"attacker","O","I-Person","Phishing"
"1211",9511,"gain","O","B-Capabilities","Phishing"
"1212",9511,"almost","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"1213",9511,"complete","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"1214",9511,"control","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"1215",9511,"over","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"1216",9511,"the","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"1217",9511,"compromised","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"1218",9511,"device","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"1219",9511,"steal","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1220",9511,"confidential","O","B-PII","Databreach"
"1221",9511,"information","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1222",9511,"the","O","B-Device","Databreach"
"1223",9511,"infected","O","I-Device","Databreach"
"1224",9511,"computer","O","I-Device","Databreach"
"1225",10322,"attackers","O","B-Person","Databreach"
"1226",10322,"use","O","B-Capabilities","Databreach"
"1227",10322,"Adwind","O","I-Capabilities","Databreach"
"1228",10322,"steal","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1229",10322,"confidential","O","B-PII","Databreach"
"1230",10322,"information","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1231",10322,"the","O","B-Device","Databreach"
"1232",10322,"infected","O","I-Device","Databreach"
"1233",10322,"computer","O","I-Device","Databreach"
"1234",837,"Ukrainian-based","O","B-Person","Databreach"
"1235",837,"hackers","O","I-Person","Databreach"
"1236",837,"Cockrell","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"1237",837,"Hill","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"1238",837,"Police","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"1239",837,"Department","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"1240",837,"server","O","B-System","Databreach"
"1241",837,"ransom","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1242",837,"last","O","B-Time","Ransom"
"1243",837,"month","O","I-Time","Ransom"
"1244",837,"resulting","O","B-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1245",837,"in","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1246",837,"the","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1247",837,"loss","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1248",837,"of","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1249",837,"video","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1250",837,"evidence","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1251",1836,"The","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1252",1836,"police","O","I-Person","Ransom"
"1253",1836,"chief","O","I-Person","Ransom"
"1254",1836,"not","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1255",1836,"to","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1256",1836,"pay","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1257",1836,"the","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1258",1836,"ransom","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1259",8564,"the","O","B-Organization","Ransom"
"1260",8564,"Cockrell","O","I-Organization","Ransom"
"1261",8564,"Hill","O","I-Organization","Ransom"
"1262",8564,"Police","O","I-Organization","Ransom"
"1263",8564,"Department","O","I-Organization","Ransom"
"1264",8564,"files","O","B-Data","Ransom"
"1265",8564,"the","O","B-System","Ransom"
"1266",8564,"server","O","I-System","Ransom"
"1267",8564,"had","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1268",8564,"been","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1269",8564,"corrupted","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1270",8564,"a","O","B-Malware","Databreach"
"1271",8564,"computer","O","I-Malware","Databreach"
"1272",8564,"virus","O","I-Malware","Databreach"
"1273",9430,"The","O","B-Purpose","Databreach"
"1274",9430,"virus","O","I-Purpose","Databreach"
"1275",9430,"had","O","I-Purpose","Databreach"
"1276",9430,"been","O","I-Purpose","Databreach"
"1277",9430,"introduced","O","I-Purpose","Databreach"
"1278",9430,"onto","O","I-Purpose","Databreach"
"1279",9430,"the","O","I-Purpose","Databreach"
"1280",9430,"network","O","I-Purpose","Databreach"
"1281",9430,"a","O","B-File","Databreach"
"1282",9430,"spam","O","I-File","Databreach"
"1283",9430,"email","O","I-File","Databreach"
"1284",9430,"had","B-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"1285",9430,"come","I-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"1286",9430,"from","I-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"1287",9430,"a","O","B-Capabilities","Phishing"
"1288",9430,"cloned","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"1289",9430,"email","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"1290",9430,"address","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"1291",9430,"imitating","B-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"1292",9430,"a","O","B-PII","Phishing"
"1293",9430,"department","O","I-PII","Phishing"
"1294",9430,"issued","O","I-PII","Phishing"
"1295",9430,"email","O","I-PII","Phishing"
"1296",9430,"address","O","I-PII","Phishing"
"1297",12334,"body","O","B-Data","Phishing"
"1298",12334,"camera","O","I-Data","Phishing"
"1299",12334,"video","O","I-Data","Phishing"
"1300",12334,"in-car","O","B-Data","Phishing"
"1301",12334,"video","O","I-Data","Phishing"
"1302",12334,"in-house","O","B-Data","Phishing"
"1303",12334,"surveillance","O","I-Data","Phishing"
"1304",12334,"video","O","I-Data","Phishing"
"1305",12334,"photographs","O","B-Data","Phishing"
"1306",12334,"the","O","B-System","Phishing"
"1307",12334,"server","O","I-System","Phishing"
"1308",12334,"were","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1309",12334,"corrupted","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1310",1793,"Google","O","B-Person","Databreach"
"1311",1793,"security","O","I-Person","Databreach"
"1312",1793,"researcher","O","I-Person","Databreach"
"1313",1793,"Tavis","O","I-Person","Databreach"
"1314",1793,"Ormandy","O","I-Person","Databreach"
"1315",1793,"discovered","B-DiscoverVulnerability","O","DiscoverVulnerability"
"1316",1793,"a","O","B-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"1317",1793,"serious","O","I-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"1318",1793,"vulnerability","O","I-Vulnerability","DiscoverVulnerability"
"1319",1793,"the","O","B-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"1320",1793,"Chrome","O","I-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"1321",1793,"extension","O","I-Software","DiscoverVulnerability"
"1322",1793,"leaves","O","B-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"1323",1793,"PCs","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"1324",1793,"wide","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"1325",1793,"open","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"1326",1793,"to","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"1327",1793,"attack","O","I-Capabilities","DiscoverVulnerability"
"1328",585,"RawPOS","O","B-Malware","DiscoverVulnerability"
"1329",585,"steal","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1330",585,"data","O","B-Data","Databreach"
"1331",585,"victims","O","B-Person","Databreach"
"1332",585,"driver","O","B-PII","Databreach"
"1333",585,"’s","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1334",585,"2-dimensional","O","B-Data","Databreach"
"1335",585,"barcode","O","I-Data","Databreach"
"1336",3580,"PoS","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1337",3580,"threats","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1338",3580,"credit","O","B-PII","Databreach"
"1339",3580,"card","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1340",3580,"mag","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1341",3580,"stripe","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1342",3580,"data","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1343",3580,"keyloggers","O","B-Malware","Databreach"
"1344",3580,"backdoors","O","B-Malware","Databreach"
"1345",3580,"get","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1346",3580,"valuable","O","B-Data","Databreach"
"1347",3580,"information","O","I-Data","Databreach"
"1348",4571,"RawPOS","O","B-Malware","Databreach"
"1349",4571,"gather","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1350",4571,"capture","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1351",4571,"the","O","B-Data","Databreach"
"1352",4571,"needed","O","I-Data","Databreach"
"1353",4571,"data","O","I-Data","Databreach"
"1354",5550,"This","O","B-Malware","Databreach"
"1355",5550,"particular","O","I-Malware","Databreach"
"1356",5550,"variant","O","I-Malware","Databreach"
"1357",5550,"collecting","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1358",5550,"data","O","B-Data","Databreach"
"1359",5550,"driver","O","B-PII","Databreach"
"1360",5550,"’s","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1361",5550,"the","O","B-GPE","Databreach"
"1362",5550,"US","O","I-GPE","Databreach"
"1363",6505,"payment","O","B-PII","Databreach"
"1364",6505,"card","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1365",6505,"data","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1366",6505,"criminals","O","B-Person","Databreach"
"1367",6505,"get","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1368",6505,"information","O","B-Data","Databreach"
"1369",6505,"victims","O","B-Person","Databreach"
"1370",6505,"full","O","B-PII","Databreach"
"1371",6505,"name","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1372",6505,"date","O","B-PII","Databreach"
"1373",6505,"of","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1374",6505,"birth","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1375",6505,"full","O","B-PII","Databreach"
"1376",6505,"address","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1377",6505,"gender","O","B-PII","Databreach"
"1378",6505,"height","O","B-PII","Databreach"
"1379",6505,"hair","O","B-PII","Databreach"
"1380",6505,"and","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1381",6505,"eye","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1382",6505,"color","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1383",4117,"a","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1384",4117,"data","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1385",4117,"breach","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1386",4117,"U.S.","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"1387",4117,"companies","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"1388",4117,"$","O","B-Money","Databreach"
"1389",4117,"7.4","O","I-Money","Databreach"
"1390",4117,"$","O","B-Money","Databreach"
"1391",4117,"lost","O","B-Data","Databreach"
"1392",4117,"or","O","I-Data","Databreach"
"1393",4117,"stolen","O","I-Data","Databreach"
"1394",4117,"record","O","I-Data","Databreach"
"1395",4117,"June","O","B-Time","Databreach"
"1396",4117,"2017","O","I-Time","Databreach"
"1397",5098,"data","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1398",5098,"breaches","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1399",7004,"hacks","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1400",7004,"this","O","B-Time","Databreach"
"1401",7004,"month","O","I-Time","Databreach"
"1402",7004,"Equifax","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"1403",7004,"Inc.","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"1404",7004,"sensitive","O","B-Data","Databreach"
"1405",7004,"data","O","I-Data","Databreach"
"1406",7004,"143","O","B-Number","Databreach"
"1407",7004,"million","O","I-Number","Databreach"
"1408",7004,"consumers","O","B-Person","Databreach"
"1409",7004,"Social","O","B-PII","Databreach"
"1410",7004,"Security","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1411",7004,"numbers","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1412",7004,"birth","O","B-PII","Databreach"
"1413",7004,"dates","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1414",7004,"was","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1415",7004,"exposed","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1416",8809,"a","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1417",8809,"ransomware","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1418",8809,"attack","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1419",8809,"cybercriminals","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1420",8809,"specialized","O","B-Malware","Ransom"
"1421",8809,"tools","O","I-Malware","Ransom"
"1422",8809,"send","B-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"1423",8809,"phishing","O","B-File","Phishing"
"1424",8809,"emails","O","I-File","Phishing"
"1425",11198,"gets","B-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"1426",11198,"through","I-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"1427",11198,"an","O","B-Person","Phishing"
"1428",11198,"employee","O","I-Person","Phishing"
"1429",11198,"clicks","O","B-Capabilities","Phishing"
"1430",11198,"on","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"1431",11198,"the","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"1432",11198,"link","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"1433",11198,"the","O","B-File","Phishing"
"1434",11198,"phishing","O","I-File","Phishing"
"1435",11198,"email","O","I-File","Phishing"
"1436",11198,"the","O","B-Purpose","Phishing"
"1437",11198,"business","O","I-Purpose","Phishing"
"1438",11198,"’","O","I-Purpose","Phishing"
"1439",11198,"network","O","I-Purpose","Phishing"
"1440",11198,"is","O","I-Purpose","Phishing"
"1441",11877,"Hackers","O","B-Person","Phishing"
"1442",11877,"encrypt","O","B-Capabilities","Phishing"
"1443",11877,"files","O","I-Capabilities","Phishing"
"1444",11877,"the","O","B-Organization","Phishing"
"1445",11877,"company","O","I-Organization","Phishing"
"1446",11877,"the","O","B-Organization","Phishing"
"1447",11877,"business","O","I-Organization","Phishing"
"1448",12478,"Hackers","O","B-Person","Phishing"
"1449",12478,"demand","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1450",12478,"payment","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1451",12478,"untraceable","O","B-PaymentMethod","Ransom"
"1452",12478,"cryptocurrency","O","I-PaymentMethod","Ransom"
"1453",12478,"like","O","I-PaymentMethod","Ransom"
"1454",12478,"Bitcoin","O","I-PaymentMethod","Ransom"
"1455",15913,"The","O","B-File","Ransom"
"1456",15913,"emails","O","I-File","Ransom"
"1457",15913,"mimic","B-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"1458",15913,"phishing","B-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"1459",15913,"campaign","I-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"1460",15913,"seeks","O","B-Purpose","Phishing"
"1461",15913,"passwords","O","I-Purpose","Phishing"
"1462",15913,"and","O","I-Purpose","Phishing"
"1463",15913,"personal","O","I-Purpose","Phishing"
"1464",15913,"information","O","I-Purpose","Phishing"
"1465",15953,"April","O","B-Time","Phishing"
"1466",15953,"Northwell","O","B-Organization","Phishing"
"1467",15953,"sent","B-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"1468",15953,"out","I-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"1469",15953,"phishing","O","B-File","Phishing"
"1470",15953,"emails","O","I-File","Phishing"
"1471",15953,"a","O","B-File","Phishing"
"1472",15953,"tax","O","I-File","Phishing"
"1473",15953,"theme","O","I-File","Phishing"
"1474",15986,"employees","O","B-Person","Phishing"
"1475",15986,"take","B-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"1476",15986,"the","I-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"1477",15986,"bait","I-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"1478",16074,"Non-Northwell","O","B-File","Phishing"
"1479",16074,"emails","O","I-File","Phishing"
"1480",16074,"pretend","B-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"1481",16074,"to","I-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"1482",16074,"be","I-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"1483",16074,"a","O","B-Person","Phishing"
"1484",16074,"colleague","O","I-Person","Phishing"
"1485",16162,"Data","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1486",16162,"leaks","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1487",16162,"Long","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"1488",16162,"Island","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"1489",16162,"companies","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"1490",16166,"2014","O","B-Time","Databreach"
"1491",16166,"Farmingdale-based","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"1492",16166,"supermarket","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"1493",16166,"Uncle","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"1494",16166,"Giuseppe","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"1495",16166,"foreign","O","B-Person","Databreach"
"1496",16166,"hackers","O","I-Person","Databreach"
"1497",16166,"had","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1498",16166,"breached","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1499",16166,"the","O","B-PII","Databreach"
"1500",16166,"credit","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1501",16166,"card","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1502",16166,"database","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1503",16166,"three","O","B-Number","Databreach"
"1504",16166,"stores","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"1505",16170,"Uncle","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"1506",16170,"Giuseppe","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"1507",16170,"the","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1508",16170,"data","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1509",16170,"breach","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1510",16170,"100","O","B-Number","Databreach"
"1511",16170,"customers","O","B-Person","Databreach"
"1512",5766,"December","O","B-Time","Databreach"
"1513",5766,"12","O","I-Time","Databreach"
"1514",5766,",","O","I-Time","Databreach"
"1515",5766,"last","O","I-Time","Databreach"
"1516",5766,"the","O","B-Person","Databreach"
"1517",5766,"crooks","O","I-Person","Databreach"
"1518",5766,"asked","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1519",5766,"for","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1520",5766,"$","O","B-Money","Ransom"
"1521",5766,"ransom","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1522",5766,"fee","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1523",10993,"an","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1524",10993,"officer","O","I-Person","Ransom"
"1525",10993,"opened","O","B-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1526",10993,"a","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1527",10993,"spam","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1528",10993,"message","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1529",10993,"a","O","B-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1530",10993,"cloned","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1531",10993,"(","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1532",10993,"spoofed","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1533",10993,")","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1534",10993,"imitating","B-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"1535",10993,"department","O","B-PII","Phishing"
"1536",10993,"issued","O","I-PII","Phishing"
"1537",10993,"email","O","I-PII","Phishing"
"1538",10993,"address","O","I-PII","Phishing"
"1539",11693,"the","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1540",11693,"ransom","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1541",11693,"demand","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1542",12319,"data","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1543",12319,"exfiltration","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1544",12319,"remote","O","B-System","Databreach"
"1545",12319,"server","O","I-System","Databreach"
"1546",541,"Personal","O","B-Data","Databreach"
"1547",541,"and","O","I-Data","Databreach"
"1548",541,"financial","O","I-Data","Databreach"
"1549",541,"data","O","I-Data","Databreach"
"1550",541,"270,000","O","B-Number","Databreach"
"1551",541,"customers","O","B-Person","Databreach"
"1552",541,"UK","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"1553",541,"payday","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"1554",541,"loan","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"1555",541,"firm","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"1556",541,"Wonga","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"1557",541,"have","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1558",541,"likely","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1559",541,"been","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1560",541,"pilfered","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1561",541,"a","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1562",541,"data","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1563",541,"breach","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1564",1540,"The","O","B-Data","Databreach"
"1565",1540,"data","O","I-Data","Databreach"
"1566",1540,"was","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1567",1540,"accessed","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1568",1540,"the","O","B-Person","Databreach"
"1569",1540,"attackers","O","I-Person","Databreach"
"1570",1540,"the","O","B-PII","Databreach"
"1571",1540,"name","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1572",1540,"e-mail","O","B-PII","Databreach"
"1573",1540,"address","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1574",1540,"home","O","B-PII","Databreach"
"1575",1540,"address","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1576",1540,"phone","O","B-PII","Databreach"
"1577",1540,"number","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1578",1540,"245,000","O","B-Number","Databreach"
"1579",1540,"customers","O","B-Person","Databreach"
"1580",1540,"the","O","B-GPE","Databreach"
"1581",1540,"UK","O","I-GPE","Databreach"
"1582",1540,"25,000","O","B-Number","Databreach"
"1583",1540,"customers","O","B-Person","Databreach"
"1584",1540,"Poland","O","B-GPE","Databreach"
"1585",1540,"the","O","B-PII","Databreach"
"1586",1540,"last","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1587",1540,"four","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1588",1540,"digits","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1589",1540,"of","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1590",1540,"their","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1591",1540,"payment","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1592",1540,"card","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1593",1540,"number","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1594",1540,"their","O","B-PII","Databreach"
"1595",1540,"bank","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1596",1540,"account","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1597",1540,"number","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1598",1540,"sort","O","B-Data","Databreach"
"1599",1540,"code","O","I-Data","Databreach"
"1600",2539,"Wonga","O","B-PII","Databreach"
"1601",2539,"account","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1602",2539,"password","O","I-PII","Databreach"
"1603",2539,"was","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1604",2539,"compromised","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1605",6462,"the","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"1606",6462,"company","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"1607",6462,"Friday","O","B-Time","Databreach"
"1608",6462,"customer","O","B-Data","Databreach"
"1609",6462,"data","O","I-Data","Databreach"
"1610",6462,"have","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1611",6462,"been","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1612",6462,"compromised","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1613",7393,"The","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"1614",7393,"company","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"1615",7393,"customers","O","B-Person","Databreach"
"1616",7393,"the","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1617",7393,"breach","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1618",7393,"Saturday","O","B-Time","Databreach"
"1619",12139,"has","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1620",12139,"been","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1621",12139,"stolen","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1622",13648,"customers","O","B-Person","Databreach"
"1623",13648,"private","O","B-Data","Databreach"
"1624",13648,"personal","O","I-Data","Databreach"
"1625",13648,"information","O","I-Data","Databreach"
"1626",13648,"was","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1627",13648,"compromised","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1628",113,"Hancock","O","B-Organization","Databreach"
"1629",113,"Health","O","I-Organization","Databreach"
"1630",113,"a","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1631",113,"cyber","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1632",113,"attack","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1633",113,"Thursday","O","B-Time","Ransom"
"1634",113,"a","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1635",113,"hacker","O","I-Person","Ransom"
"1636",113,"demanding","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1637",113,"Bitcoin","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1638",113,"hospital","O","B-Organization","Ransom"
"1639",113,"computer","O","B-System","Ransom"
"1640",113,"system","O","I-System","Ransom"
"1641",2111,"the","O","B-System","Ransom"
"1642",2111,"system","O","I-System","Ransom"
"1643",2111,"be","O","B-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1644",2111,"held","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1645",2111,"hostage","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1646",2111,"a","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1647",2111,"ransom","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1648",2111,"is","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1649",2111,"paid","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1650",3110,"The","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1651",3110,"hacker","O","I-Person","Ransom"
"1652",3110,"asked","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1653",3110,"for","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1654",3110,"Bitcoin","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1655",6050,"Friday","O","B-Time","Ransom"
"1656",6050,"afternoon","O","I-Time","Ransom"
"1657",6050,"the","O","B-System","Ransom"
"1658",6050,"network","O","I-System","Ransom"
"1659",6050,"a","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1660",6050,"ransomware","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1661",6050,"attack","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1662",6050,"an","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1663",6050,"unnamed","O","I-Person","Ransom"
"1664",6050,"hacker","O","I-Person","Ransom"
"1665",6050,"attempted","O","B-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1666",6050,"to","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1667",6050,"shut","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1668",6050,"down","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1669",6050,"(","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1670",6050,"Hancock","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1671",6050,"Health","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1672",6990,"personal","O","B-PII","Ransom"
"1673",6990,"medical","O","I-PII","Ransom"
"1674",6990,"information","O","I-PII","Ransom"
"1675",6990,"has","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1676",6990,"been","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1677",6990,"compromised","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1678",7909,"the","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1679",7909,"attack","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1680",7909,"ransom","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1681",7909,"has","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1682",7909,"been","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1683",7909,"requested","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1684",14225,"the","O","B-Organization","Ransom"
"1685",14225,"hospital","O","I-Organization","Ransom"
"1686",14225,"paying","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1687",14225,"the","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1688",14225,"ransom","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1689",15196,"private","O","B-PII","Ransom"
"1690",15196,"patient","O","I-PII","Ransom"
"1691",15196,"information","O","I-PII","Ransom"
"1692",15196,"has","B-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1693",15196,"been","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1694",15196,"compromised","I-Databreach","O","Databreach"
"1695",99,"victims","O","B-Person","Databreach"
"1696",99,"Europe","O","B-GPE","Databreach"
"1697",99,"ransomware","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1698",99,"attack","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1699",99,"demanding","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1700",99,"Bitcoin","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1701",99,"encrypted","O","B-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1702",99,"files","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1703",1098,"Bad","O","B-Malware","Ransom"
"1704",1098,"Rabbit","O","I-Malware","Ransom"
"1705",1098,"the","O","B-Malware","Ransom"
"1706",1098,"ransomware","O","I-Malware","Ransom"
"1707",1098,"demands","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1708",1098,"0.05","O","B-Money","Ransom"
"1709",1098,"BTC","O","I-Money","Ransom"
"1710",1098,"$","O","B-Money","Ransom"
"1711",1098,"computers","O","B-Device","Ransom"
"1712",4089,"the","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1713",4089,"victim","O","I-Person","Ransom"
"1714",4089,"the","O","B-Malware","Ransom"
"1715",4089,"malware","O","I-Malware","Ransom"
"1716",4089,"dropper","O","I-Malware","Ransom"
"1717",4089,"pretends","B-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"1718",4089,"to","I-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"1719",4089,"be","I-Phishing","O","Phishing"
"1720",4089,"an","O","B-Software","Phishing"
"1721",4089,"Adobe","O","I-Software","Phishing"
"1722",4089,"Flash","O","I-Software","Phishing"
"1723",4089,"installer","O","I-Software","Phishing"
"1724",6976,"Bad","O","B-Malware","Phishing"
"1725",6976,"Rabbit","O","I-Malware","Phishing"
"1726",6976,"the","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1727",6976,"latest","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1728",6976,"cyberattack","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1729",6976,"hit","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1730",6976,"Russian","O","B-GPE","Ransom"
"1731",6976,"Ukrainian","O","B-GPE","Ransom"
"1732",6976,"WannaCry","O","B-Malware","Ransom"
"1733",6976,"NotPetya","O","B-Malware","Ransom"
"1734",6976,"past","O","B-Time","Ransom"
"1735",6976,"six","O","I-Time","Ransom"
"1736",6976,"months","O","I-Time","Ransom"
"1737",7895,"The","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1738",7895,"ransom","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1739",7895,"demands","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1740",7895,"Bad","O","B-Malware","Ransom"
"1741",7895,"Rabbit","O","I-Malware","Ransom"
"1742",7895,"hackers","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1743",7895,"WannaCry","O","B-Malware","Ransom"
"1744",7895,"$","O","B-Money","Ransom"
"1745",7895,"machine","O","B-Device","Ransom"
"1746",8781,"victims","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1747",8781,"they","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1748",8781,"send","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1749",8781,"the","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1750",8781,"requisite","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1751",8781,"Bitcoins","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1752",9631,"paying","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1753",9631,"the","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1754",9631,"ransomware","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1755",9631,"amount","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1756",1099,"HACKERS","O","B-Organization","Ransom"
"1757",1099,"the","O","B-Malware","Ransom"
"1758",1099,"ransomware","O","I-Malware","Ransom"
"1759",1099,"devastated","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1760",1099,"overseas","O","B-Organization","Ransom"
"1761",1099,"banks","O","I-Organization","Ransom"
"1762",1099,"power","O","B-Organization","Ransom"
"1763",1099,"stations","O","I-Organization","Ransom"
"1764",1099,"Cadbury","O","B-Organization","Ransom"
"1765",1099,"factories","O","I-Organization","Ransom"
"1766",1099,"Australia","O","B-GPE","Ransom"
"1767",1099,"last","O","B-Time","Ransom"
"1768",1099,"week","O","I-Time","Ransom"
"1769",1099,"a","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1770",1099,"new","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1771",1099,"ransom","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1772",1099,"demand","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1773",2098,"The","O","B-File","Ransom"
"1774",2098,"new","O","I-File","Ransom"
"1775",2098,"ransom","O","I-File","Ransom"
"1776",2098,"note","O","I-File","Ransom"
"1777",2098,"demanded","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1778",2098,"a","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1779",2098,"payment","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1780",2098,"100","O","B-Money","Ransom"
"1781",2098,"Bitcoins","O","I-Money","Ransom"
"1782",2098,"$","O","B-Money","Ransom"
"1783",2098,"the","O","B-Malware","Ransom"
"1784",2098,"Petya/Goldeneye","O","I-Malware","Ransom"
"1785",2098,"malware","O","I-Malware","Ransom"
"1786",4090,"The","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1787",4090,"demand","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1788",4090,"ransomware","O","B-Malware","Ransom"
"1789",4090,"initial","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1790",4090,"request","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1791",4090,"$","O","B-Money","Ransom"
"1792",4090,"in","O","B-PaymentMethod","Ransom"
"1793",4090,"Bitcoin","O","I-PaymentMethod","Ransom"
"1794",4090,"the","O","B-Malware","Ransom"
"1795",4090,"malware","O","I-Malware","Ransom"
"1796",4090,"the","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1797",4090,"Ukraine","O","I-Person","Ransom"
"1798",4090,"last","O","B-Time","Ransom"
"1799",4090,"Tuesday","O","I-Time","Ransom"
"1800",5071,"Bitcoin","O","B-PaymentMethod","Ransom"
"1801",5071,"transactions","O","I-PaymentMethod","Ransom"
"1802",5071,"creators","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1803",5071,"$","O","B-Money","Ransom"
"1804",5071,"paid","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1805",5071,"victims","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1806",6037,"victims","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1807",6037,"paid","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1808",6037,"the","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1809",6037,"ransom","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1810",8782,"The","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1811",8782,"demand","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1812",8782,"the","O","B-Malware","Ransom"
"1813",8782,"ransomware","O","I-Malware","Ransom"
"1814",9632,"the","O","B-Malware","Ransom"
"1815",9632,"Petya","O","I-Malware","Ransom"
"1816",9632,"malware","O","I-Malware","Ransom"
"1817",9632,"kill","O","B-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1818",9632,"computers","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1819",9632,"ask","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1820",9632,"for","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1821",9632,"money","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1822",11174,"victims","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1823",11174,"pay","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1824",11174,"any","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1825",11174,"ransom","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1826",114,"Last","O","B-Time","Ransom"
"1827",114,"month","O","I-Time","Ransom"
"1828",114,"employees","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1829",114,"Colorado","O","B-Organization","Ransom"
"1830",114,"Department","O","I-Organization","Ransom"
"1831",114,"of","O","I-Organization","Ransom"
"1832",114,"Transportation","O","I-Organization","Ransom"
"1833",2112,"You","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1834",2112,"must","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1835",2112,"send","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1836",2112,"us","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1837",2112,"0.7","O","B-Money","Ransom"
"1838",2112,"BitCoin","O","I-Money","Ransom"
"1839",2112,"PC","O","B-Device","Ransom"
"1840",2112,"3","O","B-Money","Ransom"
"1841",2112,"BitCoins","O","I-Money","Ransom"
"1842",2112,"PC","O","B-Device","Ransom"
"1843",3111,"CDOT","O","B-Organization","Ransom"
"1844",3111,"is","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1845",3111,"n’t","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1846",4104,"ransomware","O","B-Malware","Ransom"
"1847",4104,"the","O","B-GPE","Ransom"
"1848",4104,"U.S.","O","I-GPE","Ransom"
"1849",4104,"internationally","O","B-GPE","Ransom"
"1850",4104,"payments","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1851",4104,"$","O","B-Money","Ransom"
"1852",4104,"1","O","I-Money","Ransom"
"1853",5085,"Hackers","O","B-Person","Ransom"
"1854",5085,"use","O","B-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1855",5085,"ransomware","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1856",5085,"to","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1857",5085,"encrypt","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1858",5085,"computer","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1859",5085,"files","O","I-Capabilities","Ransom"
"1860",5085,"demand","B-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1861",5085,"digital","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
"1862",5085,"currency","I-Ransom","O","Ransom"
